gleb
глеб
has him
у его
how to
how to
access pictures does he want to
access картин он хочет ли он
go there he wants and
туда он хочет и
year and not
год и не
so
так
kind of sits mine how a
виде садит моих how a
message
message
with a lot of cash in english-speaking
with a lot of cash in english-speaking
unity and we decided
unity and we decided
to keep your age not everyone is welcome to
to keep your age не всех приветствую на
our
наши
fabulous massashi
сказочные масаси
given  the mass is devoted exactly to marriage with
данная масса посвящено ровно по браку со
we decided to make it in this format in
мы решили сделать ее в таком формате на
Russian because we didn’t get
русском языке потому что не получили
enough questions in
достаточное количество вопросов на
English, here
английском языке вот
’s Sergey
вот сергей
blue, your first word is
синей тебе первое слово
hello to everyone, yes, I looked at the audience
всем всем привет да я посмотрел зрители
questions, that is, they concern
вопросы то есть они касаются
20 percent broke so  setting a
процентов на 20 broke so установка
patent for 50 alliance 3 from all over the network,
патент на 50 альянса 3 со всей сети вот
but over this, our fabrics will try to
но над этим наши ткани постараемся
figure out a survey,
фигасе опрос
so then let's move on to the questions of the masses, a
так тогда переходим к вопросам массах
rather large list of you has more than 25
довольно большой список вам больше 25
questions for that, our community,
вопросов для того наше сообщество
so the
так
first question is
первый вопрос
how is the situation with the funds, why
как обстоит обстановка с фондами почему
and you can see transactions if you make
и видно транзакции если совершать
any  -
какие-то сделки
that’s the deal, that’s the dad of the fund
вот папа фондом
when the collapse of the crypts began 7,
когда начался об обвал криптах 7 вот
plus something else happened literally right
плюс то еще случилось буквально сразу
after the New Year there  they began to
после новогодних там все стали
delay the terms of
затягивать сроки
crypto, the foundation began to grow and they
крипто начал основа основа расти и они
all became active again, and usually the cycle
снова все активизировались и обычно цикл
between
между
even signing the document and the delivery of
даже подписанием документа и delivery
the crypto in both directions
был крипты в обе стороны
takes more than one month, since we
занимает не один месяц так как мы этот
started this process a long time ago, that is, you
процесс начали достаточно давно то есть
don’t need to give several months, but the
не нужно дать несколько месяцев вот но
delay is January  it was total
затягивание январе было то был тотальным
because of two reasons i.e. 1 pass
из-за двух причин то есть 1 пасс
New Year holidays and the second that the
новогодние праздники и второе то что
market ended everyone began to think that what
кончился рынок все стали думать том что
is happening now the situation has
вообще происходит сейчас ситуация
returned to normal and I think the deal you will see soon
нормализовалась и думаю сделки вы скоро
cima the
cima
next question of the thread voiced the position
следующий вопрос нити озвучил позицию
that we do not need marketing important
что нам не нужны к маркетинг важно
only the price of the token when it is
только цена токина когда она будет
interesting and planned, then the people themselves will
интересна и намеченный то народ сам
come running what opinion does the alliance and ebr
прибежит какое мнение у alliance и ebr
opuses have about
опусов по этому поводу
this,
вот
if you price like the movie was
если вы цена как будто кино
growing merrily and merrily on organic
весело-весело росла на органических
deals of course this is one of the best
сделках конечно это один из лучших
marketing the problem is that it is
маркетингов проблема в том что оно так
not so  works i.e. all networks do
не работает то есть все сети делают
do marketing on the ghee
делают маркетинг на в топленом виде то
i.e. somewhere brand  ting a direct bad type
есть где-то маркетинг прямой плохой типа
like a servant to a large number of
как челядь на большое количество
audiences is a sure sign of a scam, but we
аудитории это верный признак скам а мы
don’t do that somewhere it’s bi-to-bi
так не делаем где-то это би ту би
marketing when you get
маркетинг когда у тебя появляются
media partners integrations appear
медийные партнеры появляются интеграции
you write about it to the media we started it
ты про это пишешь сми мы это начали
girl december thought you saw it all
девочка декабре дума вы все это увидели
and to
и
see more than once and
увидеть еще не раз и
the partnerships of Katya are getting warmer new
утепляется партнерства кати поход новые
projects that will already have their own audience
проекты которые будет уже свою аудиторию
and the healthiest projects they sprout
и самые здоровые проекты они прорастают
through
через
through the projector for self-study daughter
через проектор на самообучения дочь вряд
you hardly saw that someone aggressively writes
ли вы видели что кто-то агрессивно пишет
there about the ether or about the cardan, even
там про про эфир или про кардана даже
the sale itself  he never says a percentage
сама sale она никогда не говорит процент
about cinema, but usually
о кино а вот обычно с высоты на сбор
he is involved in the project from a height to collect multiplies, the
мультури занимается занимается проект
problem is that we have few projects
проблема в том что у нас проектов мало
on our own that can work, which
на самости которые могут могут работать
is why marketing is absolutely
вот поэтому безусловно маркетинг
necessary, without this, there is no way for
необходим вот без этого никак на
marketing to do axis projects
маркетинг нужно делать проекты оси
must support the pr of the entire  networks of
должна поддерживать pr всей сети
technology and do partnerships that is,
технологии и делать партнерства то есть
it's great to work in such a
это здорово галчонок работы таким
way
образом
in the well there n  and the youngest is very hot
в ну там на самом молода очень жарко
such a discussion about this,
такая дискуссия по этому поводу
which was on if the energy
которая которая была на коли по энергия
was the first part, the discussion on 2 was not
была первой части дискуссию на 2 не был
here on the mechanics, we’ll offer it clearly after both
вот на механике предложим явно после оба
sessions at the end I’ll do a few and
сессия в конце сделаю там несколько а
theses, as it seems to me, it’s right
тезисов как мне это кажется правильно
to do this globally on reforms  for
делать вот глобально по реформам вот на
luck, after the mass, I’ll tell you the
удачу после массе я расскажу
next question, nikitin’s step, voiced the
следующий вопрос никитин шаг озвучивал
following to overtake the cardan ether salon,
следующие обгонять салону карданный эфир
this is all of course funny and funny for
это все это все конечно забавно и смешно
now, for now at this stage, but
пока надо на пока на данном этапе но
even if at least we enter this race with a
даже если хотя бы мы в эту гонку вступим
wall of 5-10 dollars for talking  then it
стеной в 5-10 долларов за talking то это
will already be good the result this year is
уже будет хорошо результат в этом году
510 dollars how much is it real that
510 долларов на сколько это реально что
such a course should happen,
должно случиться такого курса
I predict the price, and even more so the cinema in
я прогнозы по цене и тем более то кино в
which we have a significant significant
котором мы имеем за значимым значимую
role I don’t give so I’ve always been very
роль не даю вот я всегда твой был очень
careful the above in the country  I
осторожен the above in страна себе
said to myself these look at it will be such a
говорил вот эти смотрите на будет такой
fit, I think that Nikita
подгонкой я думаю что никита
meant not about the price and downtime, the
подразумевала не про цену и простоем
origins even about the capitalization
истоки даже про капитализацию
about the race  for projects, that is, now
про гонка за проекты то есть сейчас
it is very important to get a project that is being
очень важно получать проект который
launched, it is necessary to conduct it here, too,
запускается надо вести и здесь как раз
but tomsk ardana there is no competition,
но томск ардана нет конкуренции там
nothing works there, nothing works here salty
ничего не ничего не работает вот солоны
even if it’s really very difficult to
даже если точно очень тяжело
drag the interior projections onto
перетаскивать проекции салона на виски
whiskey, unfortunately, but we are working on this
вот сожалению но мы над этим работаем
next question back  stapleton
следующий вопрос задник stapleton
startup plan how is it why the project
стартап план как он почему проект
failed why such a frivolous
провалился почему такой несерьёзный
approach to the request for all contacts no
подход на запрос по всем контакт никто
one answers no one knows about the project
не отвечает никто не знает ни о проекте
and there is no responsible person
и нет ответственного человека
for this because the first it was not a
на это потому что первых это был не
hackathon, that is, there was a
хакатон то есть там
stupid name there or not a mikasa holiday the
дурацкое название или не праздником
outside world  and we did this for the first time for the
микаса внешний мир и мы это первый раз
first time not the task here is the return of the
первый раз сделали not задачу вот отдачу
paste without control that’s
пасту без контроля вот что вообще
what was some kind of real format I also found out about
какой-то был реальный формат я тоже об
it myself only recently
этом сам узнал только недавно
projects left information to themselves from the
проекты оставляли информация себе от
format and the text of the video to the links baby and
формате и текст ролик ссылкам детка и
it was not a hackathon it was  something like
это был не хакатон это было что-то типа
a startup competition here, rather, a competition is not a
конкурс стартапов сюда скорей конкурс не
hackathon, well, Nick Ness was very
хакатон ну что ник несс очень
programming  there were no announced
программировал не было объявленных
tracks, there was no timing, we
треков никаких не было тайминга мы по
received about 50 applications from
итогам получили примерно 50 заявок от
potential projects as a result, and this is all
потенциальных проектов причем это все
only American projects, of
только только американские проекты из
which several projects were done through the
них несколько проектов были делать по
funnels, skip further, it was a
воронкам провороните дальше это был
new format, but it was empty unsuccessfully,
новый формат но прошло пустой неудачно
but at the same time, their funds were the same
но при этом их средства же него
spent,
потрачено
let me remind you that just guys,
давайте я напомню что просто ребят
marketing is about experiments, that is,
маркетинг это про эксперименты то есть
it was an experiment, in fact, what the
это был эксперимент собственно в чем
experiment is localized is designed
эксперимент локализованы рассчитан
only for the American market and most
только на американский рынок и большая
of the comments that come in
часть комментариев которые приходят в
groups that there is no information about this
группы о том что нет информации об этом
project and there really is no in the
проекте и нету действительно в
Russian-speaking community because
русскоязычном коммьюнити потому что
the project initially focused on the
проект изначально ориентировался на
american market and it was a chance
американский рынок и это был шанс
experiment experiment on the output of 50
эксперимент эксперимент на выходе 50
applications, which is quite good, and with zero
заявок что весьма неплохо а при нулевых
injections there is practically money, this is
вливаниях там практически денег вот
some project that is really interesting
некоторый проект действительно интересно
and
и
therefore whether they will become a recipient of
поэтому станут ли они там получатель
a fillet grant somewhere further, they will
гранта филе куда-то дальше они
advance it will be  look
продвинутся это будем смотреть
consider, but in any case, the fact that
рассматривать но в любом случае то что
activity has
активность
appeared actively quite interesting,
появилась активно достаточно интересное
this is already a good sign, of course, we will
вот это уже хороший знак конечно сделаем
draw conclusions, we will improve the
выводы будем улучшать
next question, just here, too,
следующий вопрос как раз вот тоже по
about grants, anton comes from fa to si,
поводу грантов идет антон от фа на си
voice acting is the dominant of the alliance’s methods, there is a
озвучку доминанта методов альянса стоит
queue from a company from europe and asia  but the
очередь из компании из европы и азии но
first three grants were announced for
первые три озвучены гранты получили
companies that have been in the
компании которые давно находится
community for a long time and in fact these projects will
комьюнити и по факту эти проекты будут
back stew in their own juice without an
обратно вариться в собственном соку без
external audience, a queue from Europe and
внешней аудитории очередь из европы и
Asia is a hyperbolic desire or do
азии это гиперболическое желание или же
they still exist if so, in
они все-таки существует если да то в
what quantity
каком количестве
there are a small number of projects  which
там небольшое количество проекты которые
ezru appeared earlier, we
эзру появились раньше у нас на самом
actually have a rather long process and the
деле достаточно длительный процесс и
case, that is, our business process takes
дело то есть у нас процесс дела занимает
more than a month, we all try to
больше месяца мы все стараемся его его
somehow speed it up so that it goes faster
как-то ускорить чтобы быстрее проходила
and the first projects that succumbed to this
и первые проекты которые поддались это
project are to facilitate the Russian-speaking ones,
проект облегчить русскоязычные
that is, all the funnels are not an hour  I know, that is,
то есть все воронки час не знаю то есть
Europe and Asia are close, which is right about  but
европа и азия близко что прям очередь но
also the risk of the project in the format and, well,
и риска проекта форматом а
about
примерно
two or three dozen projects, it seems to us that the projects have
два-три десятка мне кажется нам проектов
passed the problem is that, as always, the
прошло проблема еще в том что как всегда
first to receive a grant are projects with a
первый на грант прибегают проекты с
rather poor study, even
достаточно плохой проработкой даже
someone was sent for revision
кого-то отправили на доработку
, someone’s proposal was frankly turned down
предложения кого-то откровенно завернули
because  did not see any value in
потому что не увидели никакой ценности в
for the network, that is, again, the crane giving the
для сети то есть опять же кран давая
program is not a competition where
программа это не конкурсы на которых
there is necessarily a winner, but here the
обязательно там есть победитель да тут
grants
гранты
are studied much more carefully with the
исследуются гораздо более тщательно с
team several
командой проводится несколько
interviews are conducted seriously said for almost a month
собеседований всерьез сказал почти месяц
and they go through various kinds of duden and
и они проходят разного рода дюден и
to make sure that this  the project is not
чтобы убедиться что данный проект и не
some kind of rocks or some
является каким скалам или какой-нибудь
bad or orbital team with a bad
плохой или орбитальной команды с плохой
reputation, only after that
репутацией вот только после этого уже
a decision is already made about what is
принимается решение о том что ведь и
further or not, in principle, with a grant, which is
дальше или нет в принципе с грантом вот
why, in this regard, the priming process is
поэтому в этом плане процесс грунтования
much more serious than a competition for a
гораздо серьезнее чем конкурс на система
system  that most projects do not
это что большая часть проектов не
go through the funnel at this stage  oh
проходит воронку на данном этапе это
okay, so I hope that all the same, the
нормально вот и я надеюсь что все таки
efforts we are planning to take
мы усилия которую планируем принять в
this year will allow us to attract a much
этом году позволит привлечь гораздо
larger number of strong teams in the grant
большее количество сильных команд грант
system with their projects and then there will be
систему с их проектами и тогда будет все
more and more names outside the contour of Birsk
больше и больше имен вне контура бирске
its
его
next finalization question I am online 30
следующий вопрос финализации я в сети 30
seconds very  the service works slowly from
секунд очень медленно работает сервис от
it is weak,
он слаб
why if it is positioned that
почему если позиционироваться что
Iverskaya is the fastest blockchain
иверская самой быстро б ч блокчейн
to work dozens of times slower than supposedly
работать десятки раз медленнее якобы
competitors,
конкурентов
looking firstly
смотря во первых
the 1st marriage of the hero, see if the
1-я браком героем смотрите если
transaction is sent again the address is expelled
отправить транзакцию изгнана снова адрес
to another will be fast it is not 30 seconds
на другой будет быстро это не 30 секунд
obviously
очевидно
30 seconds somewhere  then 30 somewhere 10 somewhere 5,
30 секунд где-то 30 где-то 10 где-то 5
that is, there is a different exchange rate of tass,
то есть есть разная скорость обмена тасс
this is when you do this
вот это когда вы делаете делать эту
operation in the best years it was four
операцию в лучшие годы было четыре
seconds and if it was possible if it was invested in dota
секунды и если удавалось если в dota
that your address is there the address of the
вкладывалась что твой адрес там адрес
counterparty is in our wait it
контрагента находится в наше жди это
is connected  with the work of the concept, I wrote about it
связано с работой концепции я про это
many times, because I didn’t say it
писал много раз ведь тоже не говорил
either, more than once, that only after editing the
тоже не один раз что только после правки
cons  ensusa we will get all the power of the city
консенсуса мы получим всю мощь сити
which is the version up to
которая в которой является версию до
this point you have moisture
этого момента у тебя возникают влаги
between the ball to the lady and
между между шар даме и
and therefore here the inheritance transactions are so
и поэтому тут транзакции наследство так
long
долго
everything is so oranges and we will see all these
все так апельсины и мы увидим все эти
speeds
скорости которые
which should be the
которое должно быть
next question can you tell us more
следующий вопрос можно ли подробнее
the type 3 tokens of the native tokens flow to the ruin,
рассказать вам губищу перетекает тип 3
it will not affect it,
токенов нативного его это не коснется
giving then I will tell the
давая то я расскажу
native where of course it will not affect
нативный where конечно не коснется
because we are talking only about the tokens of the
потому что речь идет только про токены
token specifically now we are talking about the
токина конкретно сейчас мы говорим про
migration of the token of the standard type 3 marriage sus
миграцию токина стандарта тип 3 брак сус
on the standard type 31 date which has already
на стандарте тип 31 дата который уже
de facto become  the standard of the network and also you
де-факто стал стандартом сети и тоже ты
tea to the question is in the official
чая на вопрос находится в официальном
Jaeger repository
репозитории егерский
why you need to migrate, but I think a
почему нужно мигрировать но я думаю
lot about the same was written, they will
много про это же написали они будут
know to restore the migration process
знать восстанавливаться процесс миграция
will be for users as furious as possible,
будет для пользователей максимально бешу
that is, firstly, it
то есть во первых он
will take place around now on the 12th, the
пройдет примерно сейчас 12 числа
change will end on 15 before then  there is how you
перемена закончится 15 до то есть как вы
wrote our announcements, first of all
писали наших анонсах в первую очередь
it concerns  I am updating the vape dances,
это коснется обновление танцы vape
we will stop the farms,
мы остановим фермы
unscrew the v0 speed in order to
выкрутим скорость v0 для того чтобы
start them already with the fact that we live in liquidity
запустить их уже с тем живем ликвидности
on the new version, try to maintain
на новой версии попробовать поддерживать
the currents further, users who
уже токи дальше пользователи которые
had liquidity on the current version
было ликвидность на текущей версии
will have to disband them, because their
должны будут их расформировать ведь свои
rights on the triple, here are the ordinary
права по тройке вот и полученные обычные
currents we received  not just re-enter the new
токи нас не просто перезайти в новый
interface where they were offered to
интерфейс там где им предложенных
fanatically upgrade their talking, that
фанатически проапгрейдить их talking то
is, now we are talking about those tokens
есть сейчас мы говорим про те токина
that are actually managed and
которые собственно говоря управляются и
john brooks, here they will be automatically
джон брукс вот они будут автоматически
converted of talking of the new standard,
преобразован of talking нового стандарта
the same will approximately affect the
то же самое примерно коснется
owners of custom tokens, we are still
владельцев кастомных токенов мы пока еще
discussing  inside the mechanics how to
обсуждаем внутри механику как как
properly
правильно
upgrade them, most likely it will be some kind of
их апгрейдить по скорее всего это будет
smart contract that the
smart контракт который
authors of the token will be able to deploy by indicating
авторы токина смогут за деплоить указав
on the one hand the root address of the original one, the
с одной стороны рут адрес исходного таки
naruto address started, but they will also transfer
началась наруто адрес но и передадут
sauces to the ownership of the root of the contract, these are
соусов скри владения рут контракта это
streams for 5 smart contracts actually
потоки на 5 смарт-контракты фактически
use  The developer will just need to
пользователя нужно будет просто
send the old dota to the address of this
отправить старой dota на адрес этого
contract, in exchange I will receive new ones, so
контракта я в обмен получит новые вот
far this current working scheme is most
пока этот текущий рабочая схема скорее
likely there, if it does not change much,
всего она там если изменится не сильно
in any case, we will prepare all the
в любом случае мы подготовим все
necessary instructions for both
необходимые инструкции как для
users of our products and for the
пользователей наших продуктов так и для
creators of Tokyo, we know  after the
создателей токио вот известно после того
upgrade is
как апгрейт
completed, we will proceed with a more complex
завершён мы приступим более сложной
procedure for upgrading the beeja, here it will be
процедуре апгрейда биджа вот она будет
studied, including transferring liquidity
учатся в том числе переносит ликвидности
and
и
rear shelves, others adding
задних полках другие добавление
support for the new version of
поддержки новой версии токи
currents,
вот
respectively, the procedure is difficult
соответственно процедура сложно сложно
because there will be a lot of
тем что там достаточно много
body movements that will need to be done there, so
нужно будет сделать телодвижений поэтому
I also ask you to be understanding  that
тоже прошу отнестись с пониманием что
if some really super technical
если какие-то прям супер технические
questions during this period will not differ
вопросы в этот период отличаться не
that we don’t want to pull the
будут что мы не хотим дергать кликать
command the time of such a complex process
команду время такого сложного процесса
after that, respectively, everything that
после этого соответственно все что
the support team can answer here
сможет команда поддержки ответить здесь
we will answer to help everything will
мы будем отвечать помогать все будет
work in mode 8
работать 8 режиме
yes, they are the question apparently connected  and with this,
да они вопрос видимо связи с этим
in fact, it’s just a little
на самом деле это просто маленькая
small the mind even to the previous one that
маленькие the mind еще к предыдущему что
it’s not only about the speed of
речь не только про скорость единичных
single transactions for an individual
это транзакции для отдельного
user, the network bandwidth
пользователя мая пропускной способности
in general, that is, if
сети в целом то есть если через usb там
these transactions go through usb both outside and inside the
этой транзакции и снаружи и внутри
contracts they are dealing with
контрактами с обращаются они
indeed, they can very often
действительно могут очень очень часто
send a message in the amount, as it were, divided
кидать сообщение в сумме как бы деленное
by the time that has elapsed in detail;
на время которая прошло детально дают
from our side, sergey
технической части с нашей стороны сергей
potekhin and i will spend eight o'clock in the evening
потехин и и проведет восемь часов вечера
in moscow, therefore, it will probably be
по москве поэтому наверное надо будет
more interesting for product developers of the
более интересно разработчикам продуктов
new version of tokens, here's
новой версии токенов вот
how to carry out migration, maybe
как осуществлять миграцию может быть
you can ask yourself a question from birth,
можно по задавать себе вопрос от роду
how is it better to support your products,
как это лучше поддержать своих продуктах
that is, in general, prepare prepare your
то есть в общем готовьте готовьте свои
questions
вопросы
so the next question is
так следующий вопрос
mitya god of the hammer what have  we have six months ahead of us
митя бог молота что у нас впереди
constantly freuding in the network what are the
полгода постоянно фрейда в сети какие
main points that can be highlighted, so the
основные моменты можно выделить поэтому
question
вопрос
is to comment on what I know it concerns
вот прокомментирую что знаю это касается
and so it is their story it concerns
по так он их история это касается
consensus
консенсуса
here and this will not go anywhere there will
вот и это этому никуда не уйдем
be an update here there will be no menim
будут апдейта здесь не будет menim
yanima I will touch on the network
yanima я затрагивать сеть
plan in the form of a bank  special risks, of
плане в банке виде специальных рисков
course, this is a transition to locations and a new
это конечно переход на локации и новую
version of blocks with compression, in principle,
версию блоков с компрессии в принципе
mity about it quite well and it’s said
мити про это достаточно хорошо и сказано
because the forests call, I think it’s better to listen to it
ведь леса звони я думаю лучше его еще
again the
раз переслушать
next question and when to wait for the cold
следующий вопрос а когда ждать холодной
April
апрельской
flitton there were big plans to
флиттон были большие планы по
decentralize your Internet what
децентрализации своего интернета что
was left with  at the beginning that Stankevich and
остался при начале что станкевич и
borrowing from the coin file,
заимствованиями из файл coin
here is the right pragma, one pair is ready to
вот право pragma одна пара готов
be published
будет опубликован
at all, I expected that it would be published
вообще я ожидал что его публикуются на
that week, in fact, there is a
той неделе на самом деле там задержка
purely technical delay with uploading to the new
чисто техническая с выкладкой на новую
version of the site, now we will find out what is
версию сайта вот сейчас узнаем что там
happening there, why it takes so much
происходит почему это занимает столько
time
времени
shorter  sleep up as
короче сон до что касается
regards flitton had a bol  The main plan for
у флиттон были большой план по
decentralization on the Internet
децентрализации в интернет наверно
probably means here the question rather
имеется ввиду здесь вопрос скорее
refers to the original in the tone pen,
относится к изначальному в перу тона
if you understand the question correctly,
если правильно понял вопрос
look at the skill now for
смотрите у скилла сейчас
positioning that is not tied to the
позиционирование которое не завязаны на
work of one big match with a huge
работу одного большого матча с огромной
audience for which, in fact, tons were
аудитории для которого собственно тонн
not originally planned, of course,
изначально не планировалось конечно
some modules  which were laid there, they
какие-то модули которые там были
will probably develop, but would
наверное будут развиваться но бы
develop depending on
развиваться в зависимости от
practical use, that is, if we
практического использования то есть если
talk about the watchman,
говорить про сторож то
then again, this is not quite the same
но опять же это не совсем та бочину брок
brock sus, but I have repeatedly heard talk
суса но я неоднократно слышал разговоры
about a drive chain that will allow
про drive chain который позволит
for cheap storage of large
осуществлять дешевые хранение больших
amounts of data, including  number is necessary
объемов данных в том числе необходимо
for smart contracts, but as far as I
для smart контрактов но насколько мне
know,
известно сейчас практической разработке
nothing is being done in practical development in this part, I hope it’s
в этой части ничего не ведется я надеюсь
also useful to do a reset, maybe
тоже полезно делать сброс может быть
someone else natasha’s cross, I really
кто-то другой наташки крест я очень
hope someone else from the tsarist years
надеюсь кто-то другой царских лет
so that we already have too much
чтобы у нас и так слишком много
new perhaps  in this we will
нового возможно в это будем делать в
make this decision very much,
очень принять это решение
but in any case, if something like this
но в любом случае если что-то подобное
is taken from the original
будет браться из изначального изначально
version of this, but in any case it will be
версия про такого но влюбом случае будет
re-evaluated and adapted to the
переоценивается и адаптироваться под
new version of the
новую версию
blockchain, that's for sure it will come
блокчейна вот точно она будет исходить
from practical use and not
из практического использования а не
just for the sake of being
просто ради того чтобы был
so  the next question is
так следующий вопрос
very interesting
очень интересный
what is the status of the korean issue they were
каков статус корейского вопроса они
no longer dates in december
больше не являются были датами в декабре
they were blocked and 30 million returned
те заблокирован и 30 миллионов вернули
back to the korean ter what will happen next
обратно корейскому теру что будет дальше
with this amount but if you
с этой суммой но если вы внимательно
look carefully you
посмотрите то
need attacks on which were carried out on one
надо атаки на которые велись на один
address then they returned and then  they
адрес потом они вернулись и потом они
spread over the
растеклись по
tenants a diploma, that is, 30 million
арендаторам диплом то есть 30 миллионов
lie on the
лежат на полах
floors from there they move periodically
вот оттуда они двигаются периодически
here the guys try farming
вот ребята пробует farming
did the wrong farming they entered
сделали неправильный farming вошли
including us with one leg on that's because
включая нас одной ноге на вот потому что
they don't know how to do it right with
они не умеют правильно делать с
the truth of the consultation to find not
установим правде консультации обрести не
about two legs as in principle  work
про две ноги как в принципе работают
here and in principle in cor  she was there there was a
вот и в принципе в корее был там был
split there we were sitting at the risk that
раскол там мы сидели в рисках того что
all this would spill over into the market it didn’t spill over the
это все выльется в рынок она не вылилось
Korean community reformatted es
корейской комьюнити переформатировал ась
that’s why the Korean to the Korean
вот и поэтому корейское к корейской
community now she’s there again everything is ok
комьюнити сейчас она снова там все окей
they have a new leader and they have a very
у них новый лидер вот и с ними очень
good relationship
хорошие отношения
thanks yes  this was one of such very
спасибо да это был один из таких очень
important questions discussing the latest
важных вопросов обсуждаем последние
farming meet the
пофармить встречать
next question your opinion will the
следующий вопрос ваше мнение удастся ли
new centers succeed in the flex exchange this
новый центрами но на бирже flex в этом
year it will be fully launched this year and also
году полноценно запустится а также
gain popularity we know
приобрести популярность мы ведь знаем
that maps is a strong point, this development of
что конек по maps эта разработка
high-loaded networks they promote
высоконагруженных сетей они продвижения
in the market means in
на рынке значит в этом проекте должны
many companies should be involved in this project,
быть задействованы многие компании
for example, the miner gate
например майнер gate
here, but if
вот но если
again the question is rather not for me here is flex
опять вопрос скорее не ко мне вот flex
flex then what it will appear and there it is
flex то что он появится и и там него там
sure the question of time when it will appear
уверен вопрос времени когда появится
if flex will work since things are on
если flex будет работать так как вещи на
what, well, the speed is over  everything
что ну плане скорость это зак всего
else, then we will all help
остального то мы все будем помогать
promotions, but
продвижений а
because, in principle, there are taxes d  about what
потому что в принципе есть налоги до что
now, in fact, there is a serum, and above it
сейчас по сути есть serum да и над ним
there on the fat is not up to its flex, and only 1
там на сало не до его flex и и только 1
city works like this before the start, is the
city так работает до начала ли
alternative flex on the
альтернатива flex на
skewers, but this is a very strong panda
вертели а вот это очень сильно панда
to sit down
сесть
here, we wish you good luck in finishing so that you can
тут пожелаем удачи в завершении чтобы
work out the
отработал
next question what are you  you can say
следующий вопрос что вы можете сказать
at the expense of convex your se
за счет convex свои se
instead of g am saw how
вместо g am увидели как туда через мост
745 thousand non-children were driven there across the bridge
745 тысяч не из детей
that is suspected lost they stole
что подозревается потерянном угнали
for this I wanted to say yes,
для этого хотел сказать да
in fact, if you closely
на самом деле если бы вы внимательно
follow the updates of the bridge, then the bridge was the
следить за обновлениями бриджа то бриджа
first to appear a few months ago
несколько месяцев назад первых появился
governance interface  up to which there
governance интерфейс до в котором
is
ведется
quite interesting activity, and
достаточным интересно активность да и
everything about the pose you are introduced there is not
все про поза вы которые там вносятся не
introduced by a sufficiently clear
вносится достаточно понятным
justification and explanations of how it
обоснованием и объяснениям как это
works, plus on our github
работает плюс на нашем гитхабе
regarding specifically the comic three
касательно конкретно комикс три
strategies
стратегии
there is a whole document that explains
есть целый документ который объясняет
how it works why it works if it’s
как работает почему это работает если по
simple then a
простому то
comic  3 service is a strategy with a
комикс 3 сервиз это стратегия с
fairly good profitability of us you are
достаточно неплохой доходностью нас ты
dead  so, by
покойных вот и соответственно
consensus, yes, the bridge decided
консенсусом да у бриджа было решено
to direct 10 percent of the liquidity of the
направить 10 процентов от ликвидности
locked bullets to this strategy
залоченных пули ю с д т в эту стратегию
until directly from it and
до непосредственно это собственно из и
it was originally the
было изначально
business model of the entire bridge that part of the
бизнес-модель всего бриджи что часть
liquidity that is locked in bolts
ликвидности который залочены в болтах
will be invested in low-risk
будет вкладываться в низкой рисковые
protocols for  in order to generate
протоколы для того чтобы генерировать
profitability for releasers and for
доходность для релизеров и для стикеров
stickers, respectively, this strategy is the first
вот соответственно эта стратегия первая
of many is obviously a given and of course
из многих очевидно данность и мы конечно
we are doing deep research carefully
делаем глубокие research внимательно
studying the network we have spent looking at how
изучаем сеть истратили смотрим насколько
stable profitability is how high the
устойчивая доходность насколько большой
level of liquidity of the end is kept so as
уровень ликвидности конца держится чтобы
not to be a movable risk to security officers permit
не быть подвижным риском чекистам permit
losses of everything else
лоссов всего остального
[music  ]
[музыка]
in any case, the mechanisms of this strategy,
в любом случае механизмы этой стратегии
they are all in the public domain, they
они все находятся в открытом доступе они
were really ravana, I’ll
были правде раваны
comment yes, yes, I was waiting for a safari of the Russian Federation,
прокомментирую да да ждало сафари рф
there are funds, for example, in the same war, yes, that
есть фонды например в тот же war да то
is, which in this strategy holds not a
есть который в этой стратегии держит ни
single million dollars for a long time and
один миллион долларов давно и
there are guys like they stick to rice  in  other
есть ребята как и держатся риса в других
strategies and therefore this model of the bridge,
стратегиях и поэтому эта модель бриджа
that is, we are part of the assets that are
то есть мы часть активов которые
locked through the yorn narrow rolls, which are
залочены через йорн узкие валки которые
also fitna there for a long time, the truth is ravana and
тоже там фитна давно правде раваны и
somehow here your finance we will
как-то вот your finance мы их будем
place them in different strategies and in
размещать других в разных стратегиях и в
this strategy, that is, it concerns the ether of the
этом стратегия то есть это касается эфир
brain  As for now, there is a lot of cardan there,
брэда касается сейчас кардана много там
like todos, there’s nowhere
вроде todos тыкаться там особо некуда
to put it, and just part of the remnants
размещать и как раз часть остатков
are in these networks and annihilate the
находится в в этих сетях и аннигилируют
profitability later, which is distributed
доходность потом который распределяется
if all the bridge holder is then the reason
ли все холдер бриджа то при то причина
why the bridge is growing there and why there
почему там bridge растет и почему там
are appearing there, but we still don’t have new players  we
появляются но новой игроки мы еще не в
fully unpacked the entire
полной мере распаковали вот вообще всю
chain of the bridge, that is, if the strategies
цепочку бриджа то есть если стратегиях
need to work a little because of what
нужно работать немножко из-за того что
needs to be done, the update started, that’s the fact that
нужно сделать начал апдейта вот то что
the same notorious type type 31 after
тот самый пресловутый тип тип 31 после
it we will roll out three strategies
него будем раскатывать три стратегии
further the
дальше
next question is where, having given the alliance, it happens to
следующий вопрос куда дав альянс бывает
put the surpluses and
девает излишки и
the question is
вопрос
an excess of microcurrents on the market, someone is
избыток микротоки на рынке кто-то
buying
покупают
someone else now it’s a little different
кто то кто то сейчас чуть по-другому это
it works, that is, we have
работает то есть у нас есть
a fab fund before which there is a lot of
фонд fab до в которой находится много
liquidity and, in fact, we
ликвидности и по сути вокруг него
had to balance
пришлось а балансировка
it, that is, it is obvious that if the tokens are pouring
то есть очевидно что если токены льется
on the market, yes, that is, they go especially not
на рынке да то есть они идут особо не
here on the exchanges, then there is an arbitrator
тут на биржах потом возникает арбитра
zhora and,
жора и
in fact, an alliance of snow  degree the price keeps
по сути альянс снега степени цену держит
its faces with its liquidity and the
свои лица своей ликвидностью и
liquidity of our users all
ликвидностью наших пользователей все
who hold juice money the
которые которые держат деньги сока
next question is what is your plan in
следующий вопрос такой какой ваш план на
case one of the bridges of the
случай если вдруг один из мостов
hypothetical hakuouki suddenly steals funds
гипотетических hakuouki уведут средства
look so
смотри так
here it is here not just to
вот он здесь здесь не просто по нужно
condemn the current protection mechanism that
осуждала действующий механизм защиты то
is  well, firstly, there is a limit, and that is,
есть ну во первых есть лимит а то есть
there is sufficient verification by them,
есть есть ними достаточной верификации
so it’s physically impossible to withdraw everything
поэтому вывести все и физически
if some kind of
невозможно если возникает какая-то
large transaction occurs, then we look at what kind
большая транзакция то мы смотрим что это
of transaction it is, we have specially
за транзакция у нас есть специально
issued roles for people of the guard bridges, but
выданные роли людей гварды бриджи а вот
which are taken apart in case it suddenly happens
которые разбирают на случай вдруг это
there was a potential break-in, there were no such
был потенциально взлом вот таких
situations,
ситуаций не было
but in any case they keep  We
вот но в любом случае держать бардов нам
have to bards so that everything is calm in the
приходится для того чтобы все спокойно
field,
полю
but yes, and, accordingly, the limits are
но и да и соответственно лимиты
dynamic, that is, they depend on the
динамические то есть они зависят от
overall ability of the bridge, so I’m not of
общей способности бриджа вот я не
course periodically reviewed, that
конечно периодически пересматриваются то
is, so that the brain can scale to the
есть чтобы мозг мог масштабироваться под
demands of the market,
запросы рынка
yes, I’ll say more in almost any mode,
я да я скажу больше почти в любом режиме
then  and if verification is acceptable from
то и если что верификации допустим из
the same and weighty polygon there,
того же и веские там полигона там
there will be money far from instantly, too,
найдутся деньги далеко не мгновенно тоже
for this reason, that is, small
по этой причине то есть мелкие
transactions are all automatic, but big
транзакции все на автомате а вот больших
rules are sorted out
правил разбираются
[music] the
[музыка]
next question is when a new Polina tones is planned for
следующий вопрос когда планируется новый
dads and
полина tones пап и денег
money after after  tokens, now we
вот после после токенов то сейчас у нас
have a lot of things slowed down by this
этим очень многие вещи тормозились то
, that is, we could not fully work for this
есть мы не могли за это полноценно
from annoyance and the bench of the cardan,
работать с досады и скамейки кардана
we could not fully, but knowing that
мы не могли полноценно но зная чтобы
this duet we did not do anything in style,
этот дуэт мы ничего не ли стиле в том
including only increases the overall overall
числе только увеличивает общую общую
entropy of all, that is, a couple  so that the
энтропию всех то есть пара чтобы
procedure after after the update is the whole
процедура после после апдейта вот вся
queue of which there is, it will pass and on
очередь которой есть она пройдет и на
fpl filmed a couple of new
fpl снимала пар новых
ri  dera leaving the bridge for what merits a
ридера покинув bridge за какие заслуги
friend is counted so only
друг таким лишь
these currents are received by those who used the
получают эти токи на тех кто пользовался
bridge in the early stages of the
мостом на ранних этапах провайдера
liquidity provider,
ликвидности
therefore, before the liquidity provider, most
поэтому до провайдера ликвидности скорее
likely we will update the
всего мы будем делать апдейт формулы
output formula so that new providers are also
вывод с тем чтобы новые провайдеры тоже
not separated,
не были отделены
probably on the next fraction in the robot  according to the
наверное на следующем дробь в роботе по
new mechanism, the
новому механизму
next question is about partners that
следующий вопрос касательно партнерс что
again with a promising partnership there is little
снова с многообещающим партнерством мало
world with it from the partnership’s nose,
world с она со ска нос у
that’s what now even more
партнерства вот чего сейчас даже более
similar questions the partner was
подобные вопросов партнер была мода
all sorts of different fashion
всяких разных вот про вообще сознание
, there’s so much
так много
about consciousness in general, but although I might leave, I didn’t
вот но хотя может отъеду запакую не
see it, and therefore we  in the concert
видел и поэтому мы в концертном
proposal which concerns the agreement
предложения который касается договор
among our partners the
числе наших партнеров
next question is the same about
следующий вопрос тоже самое по поводу
one partnership it was a partnership
одного партнерства это было партнерство
with the dunes
с дюны
where the developers of the zone or swap it is a
где разработчики зоны или swap это
purchase a purchase in quotes Mr. de
покупка покупка в кавычках г-на де
developers friend
разработчики friend
here a meeting similarly, that is, I was not
здесь встречу аналогично то есть я не
the initiator of this partnership it
был инициатором этого партнерства нее
things are not freela  nder
дела не freelander
here is their test on there, as far as I
вот их тесто на там на то насколько я
know, where the network promised a
знаю там где network много чего обещал
lot of things a lot of things did not do what you promised
много чего не сделал того что обещала
to do partially, and that's why we
сделать вы частично а вот и поэтому мы
will offer a lament set, but this, too,
будем предлагать сет lament но это тоже
let's also at the end
давай тоже в конце про все партнерки
so it will be
ноги могут заспойлерить из так будет
quick and let's lose thirty
быстрого и давай его потерял thirty не
not completely
до конца
[laugh]
[смех]
twirl over save
вертай над сохранить
but
но
I'm all club
я все club это
these are these projects I think that addressing the
эти проекты я думаю что адресовать
question of how they directly
вопрос тем как непосредственно их
offered
предлагал
them would be more honest and fair
это будет более честным и справедливым
horde don't spend what in what I want to
орда не тратят что в том что хочу
offer on  global govanus, yes, that is, a
предложить на global гованус да то есть
package, and we started, to some extent, the
пакет а мы начинали в некой степени
Italian legs of the cheese reform,
итальянского ногам сырной реформы
which concerned both
которые касались и
changes and did not sew, including
изменения и не шило в том числе вот и
helping to stop
способствовать тому чтобы перестали
thoughtlessly giving away tokens, that is, the
бездумно отдаваться токены то есть
rule has become tougher and everyone understood
правило все ужесточились и все понял
that something does not work as it is  but part of the
что-то не работает как есть но часть
reforms was not completed, the boss was also a
реформ не была закончена босс тоже был
type of thing and rethink that's
тип вещь и переосмыслить вот поэтому что
why to propose to do we formulate in
бы предлагать сделать формулируем
writing google governa  nce well, there 1 before that, do more substitutions 2 and not [ __ ], let it turn out in Korea very Japan, an ugly situation, and there those who were with us in general with the network at the start, they are not quite with us now, that’s why there you need to change not shilov for those who as if by deed he proves about his love a trick to Kyiv and by his actions this change of two they are [ __ ] this is the first action in the form the second action as for affiliates 80 percent of affiliates did not give anything at all nothing here 10 percent of affiliates gave something but not so much how much they received tokens in terms of underwear and 10 percent of affiliate programs, at best they gave more for the performers than they received tokens, the networks were killed and the question was the partner of the si team for a long time, that is, we can’t even fully calculate all the obligations of the elephant network for all partners because everyone is different now it will not execute unknown ones, someone starts trying to get tokens by giving out reports, hits the port is normal, some are not, but in general
письменно google governance ну там 1 до
it became clear that affiliate programs, I’m probably not
стало понятно что партнерки я наверно не
the best tool for work, yes, that
самый лучший инструмент работы да то
is, it was a grandiose experiment
есть это был грандиозный эксперимент
that I wanted Ivanovich to show for
который показал хочу мог иванович для
me in Prague
меня в праге про компании я вас кого
were already carried out thanks to the analyst
проводились уже спасибо нари аналитик
analysis of the callanetics collected here
анализе калланетик собрано сюда которые
who sorted it out there that 80 percent is
там поразбирали что процентов 80
permanently closed, that is, it
постоянно закрыть то есть там написать
won’t be there to write all the guys talking at all, and the
все guys talking не будет совсем вот и
partner program is closing,
партнерка закрывается
watch out specifically that it’s just
следите за специально что это просто
move it for a long time it hangs for a long time, what the hell,
подвиньте давно висит до какого хрена
you just need to cut it the remaining 20
просто надо его разрубить остальные 20
percent  a partner who may have
процентов партнера который может быть
done something there,
там что-то сделали там разобрать
weigh it up and do it with everyone
взвесить и со всеми сделать это
with someone from this motorcycle that the guys
с кем-то с этого мотоцикла что вот ребят
run to the water of such and such a thing
добегаете до воду такой-то штуки
to get such and such a volume and guess and you you
получать такой то объем и угадаю и вы вы
you you you you you you will get and  then when
вы вы вы вы вы получите и тогда когда
you make yours there now maybe 5
сделаете там своей теперь может быть 5
perry looks with someone from this we
перри смотрится с кем-то из этого мы
cycle  here’s the last tranche for the guys,
цикл вот на ребята последний транш
now forward, now forward,
дальше вот вперед сейчас вот вперед на
business on grants is falling for the night, that is,
ночь падает бизнес на гранты то есть
try using other models, I could
пробуйте по другим моделям я мог
try to earn networks
попробовать заработать сети и
and prolong affiliate debts, it
на пролонгировать партнерки долги
probably doesn’t make sense, that is, either a set
наверно смысла нет то есть либо сет
moment, each of the partners who locked the
момент каждый из партнеров которые запер
form, whether they go anywhere  didn’t disappear or
форме ли которые никуда не исчезли либо
just close the affiliate program that did
просто партнерке закрыть которые сделали
nothing, that is, the list is now
ничего то есть список сейчас пока у нас
going around inside us and not [ __ ], so we elect
ходит внутри и не шалав вот мы избираем
as soon as there is something similar to
как только будет что-то похожее на
consensus, then this list will be
консенсус то это список будет
published to everyone in order to collect
опубликован всем чтобы еще до собрать
bags of the community even before the
bags комьюнити
third is reforming with the renovationists
третье это реформирования с обновленцев
the question has also been hanging in the air for a very long time,
тоже вопрос очень очень давно висит в
but it’s hard to live to move forward
воздухе а тяжело жить двигаться вперед
when you have a lot of suffocating air
когда у тебя очень много сыщет воздухе
here, too, the majority will have such a proposal to
здесь тоже будет такое предложение у
close because they have not
большинства закрыть потому что они не
done anything and there is no life there.
сделали ничего и там же жизни нет я тут
of there is a message for
в туле ambassador of там сообщение
half a year there is no reason for mass if yes
полгода нет повода за массовое если да
there is no choice of messages here there are  it
нет выбора сообщений вот естественно при
would be obvious that those that immediately close the
бы очевидно что такие что закрывают
unimportant ones dropped out of the name, it is important
сразу неважных выбыла из название важно
that they did, in fact,
что они делали по сути
some collected to reformat, that
какие-то собрал переформатировать то
is, to some more commercial
есть на более какую-то коммерческую
model, that is, for example, there is a
модель то есть к примеру есть
chance then formally verification, but
шанс потом формально верификации да
no matter how yours is on how they are  sexy
как бы не ваш на как они сексуальны
verification or audit is necessary for every
верификацию или аудит это нужно каждому
project in the network
проект в сети
to make them service models, that is,
сделать их сервисными моделями то есть
so that projects can access them as an autograph service
чтобы к ним как сервис автограф
for a clear formal
обращались проекты к ясному за формально
verification and make subsidies there
верификация и сделать там дотации потому
because usually in the same world you will receive an
что обычно в том же мире вы получите
audit for free, that is, a formal order
аудит бесплатно то есть формально приказ
can be  in general, it’s completely free
может быть вообще полностью бесплатно
or symbolic to take projects of
или символических брать проектов
some kind to look at, maybe 10, and
какой-то чем посмотрите может быть 10 и
in this format, that is, this format,
в таком формате то есть такой формат
continue working, that is, everyone
продолжить работу то есть у каждого
gathered should have a lot of shouting
собрался должно быть множество кричите
without non-customers who ask you Kosovo
без не заказчиков которые косово вам
for some kind of service, maybe
обращаются за неким сервисом может быть
and collected to call in general  in another way, not
и собрал называть вообще по-другому не
sugar runs a rotten this guild
sugar runs a загнили этой гильдии
is called yes we can name it  to give a dow
называется да у нас можно назвать доу
or another room call something interesting to
или еще комната звони интересное
come up with for this entity there should
придумать для этой сущности на должны
be a group of people professionals in their
быть группа людей профессионалов в своей
field
области
who, as a service for a fee, work as
которые как сервис за оплату работают
businesses that are inside the network that
бизнесами которые внутри сети которые
come from outside and this activity
приходят извне и эта деятельность
somewhere can be completely dated
где-то полностью может быть датироваться
from the game rocket partially one fifty-  fifty
из game ракета частично один фифти-фифти
for
например
example this sentence
вот такое предложение
sounds great help 8 new
звучит помогу превосходно 8 новый
comment in was just minutes like this
комментарий в был как раз и минут таком
thanks for the big spoiler i think our
спасибо за большой спойлер я думаю наше
statement is
заявление
[laughter]
[смех]
so let's move on to the next question
так переходим к следующим вопросом так
so lately there has been a strong
за последнее время замечено сильная
activity of the bot not he was able to
активность работы бота not он смог
which all turn  does not
которых все очередь делает не
expedient work of arbitrageurs do not
целесообразную работу арбитражников не
keep up with him does it have to do
поспевают за ним имеет ли бороться с
with this bot or is it private
отношение к этому боту либо это частный
that’s his and your attitude to the work of
вот его-то и ваше отношение к работе
such bots who told you that this
подобных бот кто вам сказал что этот
one will be there there in the top ten there are
один будет там там вот в десятке там
tens if not hundreds in fact  in fact
десятки если не сотни на самом деле
hundreds no dozens we lived we did the
сотен нет десятки мы жили мы сделали
analysis for the last time not recorded
разбор на последний раз не записано
dolat  three years
делать три назад
ago, two months ago, there were then 15
вот два месяца назад было тогда вам 15
bots that we discovered
ботов которые которые мы обнаружили
that often do a lot of actions,
которые делают часто много действий
some kind of cross inside the exchange, some with
какие то кросс внутри бирже какие-то с
other exchanges, I remember that I still don’t
другими биржами я вспомню что еще не
like some lying around, too, there were
нравится какой-то поваляется тоже были
transactions,
сделки
in fact, now modern
на самом деле сейчас современной
arbitrage is arbitrage nerd, that is, of
арбитраж это арбитраж ботан то есть как
course, you can try to keep up
бы конечно можно пробовать успевать или
or with your hands, but usually it doesn’t
ними руками но обычно это так не
work that way, that is, now it’s really possible
работает то есть сейчас реально наружу
to get outside those who can
получить те кто может все
automate everything, and in fact it’s
автоматизировать и на самом деле это
cool because it allows you to better
классно потому что это позволяет лучше
synchronize prices on the market, and that’s it
синхронизировать цены на рынке да и вот
as Serezhe said earlier that we are
как сереже там раньше сказал что мы
now focusing as an alliance, we have the
сейчас как альянс фокусируемся имеем
opportunity to focus on working with
возможность фокусироваться на работе с
tone swap, because we know that due
тон свапом потому что мы знаем что за
to these measures, the stained glass mechanisms, the
счет вот этих мер витражных механизмы
guys automatically regulate
пацаны автоматически регулировать по
throughout the market, and this sagari is very
всему рынку вот и это сагари очень
convenient, so it’s like this is
удобно поэтому это же как бы это
normal  the phenomenon on the market is good
нормальное явление на рынке это хорошо
thanks
спасибо
next question what about sting bija
следующий вопрос что со стингом биджа
when it will be understood  I’m on the verge of
когда появится понимание по на грани за
staking,
стекинг
I can put 1 distribution, but there was already,
поставить могу 1 дистрибьюшен же уже был
that is, they should get jarils and all the
то есть там должны получить ярилы и всех
bones as you shave, he was not too
костей как бреешь он был не слишком
close, it was because we didn’t have time to
ближе это был потому что мы мы не успели
make the
сделать
next distribution, it might
следующий дистрибьюшен будет то может
be small, so we will do it like
быть небольшой поэтому мы сделаем как
this  will give a subsidy from closer just from the
это даст дотацию из ближе как раз с
first strategy 3 servos who
первой стратегии 3 серве которые
said and further the size of the
говорили и дальше уже размер дивидендов
bridge dividends will grow as the hotel increases
бриджа будет расти по мере увеличения
but the trills connected to the strategy,
но трелей подключенных стратегию
respectively, we really were
соответственно мы дествительно были
taken into account the constrained update of the bridge to the
учтены скованные обновление бриджа под
new standard, now
новый стандарт окинув вот сейчас
finally we will have our hands  unleashed
наконец-то у насти руки будут развязаны
and the next few months, I think
и ближайшие несколько месяцев я думаю
that but as we see several new
что но как видим несколько новых
strategies to add to the bridge, which will allow
стратегий добавить на бридж что позволит
more efficient use of the
более эффективно использовать
liquidity that is in the windrows and of
ликвидность которые есть в валках ну и
course,
конечно
work on increasing the creation of the bridge
работа над увеличением творила бриджа
is a woody priority for us this
это древесных приоритета для нас на этот
year actually somehow in the mouth ,  the question was
год собственно как-то в рот , было
stated
заявлено
whether the vinegar was to run
вопрос планирует либо уксус запустить
steam over it could  from kiwi pisi to the
пару над он смог с киви писи до
manifestation of
проявления flexo
flexo, I wouldn’t be against the St. Petersburg BBC,
она я бы я был не против питерских би си
take it discussed that’s why
возьмите это обсуждали вот поэтому
now now our standards have become
теперь сейчас наши стандарты стали
somewhat closer to each other that’s why
несколько ближе друг другу вот поэтому я
I won’t forbid them the summit will say we’ll
я не то им запрещу саммите скажет
launch we’ll launch it for
запускаем запускаем у
me it will be without I can’t do it
меня это будет без сделать не могу
to do it, but apparently someone asked just
сделать но видимо кто-то задавал просто
plastic why he probably had something
пластика зачем наверно у него что почти
to sell almost immediately,
продать сразу
apparently this is the first first thing,
видимо это первая первую очередь разлог
but
а
it still needs
это таки надо
to be a question when it is planned to add a
встать вопрос когда планируется добавить
swap tone exchange to which market, like
биржу тон swap на кой market как и
other aggregates, the market index
другие агрегаты рынку индекс
here is how we would  dex never
здесь есть вот как бы мы dex никогда не
added, especially dex on the new network,
добавляли тем более dex на новой сети
that's why it's interesting at first we went
вот потому интересного сначала мы пошли
to the sim psycho inteco here with you add
на сим психу интеко вот с вами добавьте
something by the fall still naturally but in the fall
то к осени еще вот естественно но осенью
on the wild was earlier when you can
на диком был ранее когда ты можешь
add something on the air another dex
добавить что-то на эфире очередной dex
butyrate to do this  we don’t need any thousands of
бутират это делать не надо никаких тысяч
integrations, we ended up in a very
интеграцией мы попали в очень звучит
long queue
длинную очередь
when, relatively speaking, the course of our
когда условно говоря курсе наших
purchases, they became at least somehow like
покупали они стали хотя бы как-то как
it immediately became much easier for someone to talk
как-то разговаривать стало сразу сильно
, that is, in order for all this to
проще вот то есть для того чтобы все это
happen, that is, since it also came out that
случилось то есть так как тоже вышел что
I
симсе
take the Sims and the baby with the file, and therefore, first of
и детка беру с файлом и поэтому в первую
all, you need to settle well there
очередь надо там хорошо обосноваться
so that again you need to give the account the
чтобы снова ца там нужно счет давать
data in the correct form  and
данных загров правильном виде и вот
then this procedure will pass, or a wise
тогда эта процедура пройдет или мудрой
timer for vodka 112, also when everyone, well, the
таймер на водку 112 также когда всех ну
priority is that tasks are important, therefore,
приоритет вот задач важно поэтому и
we are engaged in that we went the wrong way,
занимаемся что мы пошли по неправильному
not the right algorithm, because
не по правильный алгоритм потому что мы
we stupidly didn’t know it
его тупо не знали
well, and locally we will of course
ну и местно там уже будем конечно
go there with new names  products
заходить с новыми названиями продуктов
that we are also very soon correct until it is
которые мы тоже очень скоро верен до это
logical after a complete
логично после полного таскает
rebranding the
ребрендинга
next question of
следующий вопрос
sergey bridge when she why the comments of
сергея мост когда она зачем комменте
cardan moscow places the reason is only a
кардана moscow места причина только в
decrease in the transfer commission,
уменьшении комиссия за перевод
then it will be interesting only for very
то это будет интересно только на очень
large volumes, but if you are sure
большие объемы а если уверенность в том
that large volumes and  liquidity will be
что большие объемы и ликвидности будут
transferred to a little-known
перевел переливать в малоизвестный
project,
проект
but they don’t need a cardan at all
но и verse кил им вообще не нужен
where was a friend, but first, if
кардана где была другом но первое если
you can change it now and
вы сейчас можете изменить а кардена
transfer this movie to another network,
перегнать это кино в другую сеть
show
покажите как это сделать
how to do it.
вот потому что в кардан ность посмотрите
carefully there, well, there would have been
внимательно там ну вот был было бы с
discussions launched with pomp that
помпой запущен дискуссий который
stopped working after the first
перестал работать после первой
transaction 70, which
транзакции 70
is why there is an Iberian gateway to them,
вот поэтому там иверский до них это шлюз
that is, naturally, part of the liquidity
то есть естественно часть ликвидности
will settle, and we have, among other things
будет оседать и у нас вот в том числе
, a garden made for this, and part will
для этого сделанных сада а часть будет
go in transit from
идти транзитом из
cardans other networks,
карданов другие сети
that is, if someone knows how now
то есть если кто то знает как сейчас
when to withdraw money to the landfill,
когда на вывести деньги в полигон дайте
please, when buying, write in a personal
пожалуйста покупая напишите в личку
beautifully when we started rudder it was
красиво когда мы начинали rudder был
definitely not possible
точно нельзя
here on many ga-100 questions did not know
вот на на многих ga-100 вопросы не знали
so the
так
next question is
следующий вопрос
regarding what with what with projects
касательно что с что с проектами токен
giving the token and factum both tokens are
отдав и factum оба токина есть
official lists talking tom's dad
официальный списков talking tom's папа
here is a very oriental hurry about what  Well,
вот очень восточном спешным о чем вот
in the end, the guys decided
ребята в итоге решили
not to launch as they planned,
не запускаться как планировали вот по
because of the crazy wigle social
причине сумасшедших wigle социальных
risks, and in this project after that, it’s
рисков и на в этом проекте после вот
fresh and for everyone, so the toten just
свежими и всем поэтому тотен просто
hangs here, but we’ll probably clean it up,
висит вот но наверное мы будем очищать
you can remove it and burn it, it doesn’t make
можно его убрать и сжечь он не имеет
sense
смысла
as for exactly the same  having pressed it, it
что касается точно таки надав это
was probably my personal mistake and
наверное была моя личная ошибка да на то
that it started and appeared, that’s
чтобы он запустился и появился вот
why now we are doing very
поэтому теперь мы делаем очень
carefully the morons of everything, that is, I
внимательно всего вся то есть я
believed the guys that they
поверил ребятам что они быстро все
will do everything quickly, this hasn’t happened for
сделаю вот этого не произошло уже прошло
half a year, that’s why the attention of the tokens
полгода вот поэтому внимание токены
is somehow distributed  inside with a shadow, here
как-то распределились внутри с тенью вот
I have it too, that's why the
есть у меня тоже есть вот поэтому
currents above will remain, well, that it hangs on
токи над останется ну что он висит на
different wallets, maybe all the same
разных кошелька может быть все таки
guys, when it ends at the end I will
ребята когда ему конце на сделаю запуск
launch it, and then it will already be possible to drink to learn to
вот и тогда уже можно будет пить учиться
do,
делать
but in principle, this is now also nothing
но в принципе это вот сейчас тоже ничего
advice  we will have a state of emergency in the dash ecosystem
совета у нас появится в экосистеме dash
on me soon enough and
на меня дело чп от до достаточно скоро и
the game will start mimers kelly
начнется начнётся игра мимерс келли
who were not inside yet  here it
которые еще внутри не было вот
is called investing some project
называется инвестирует какой-то проект
at some stage
на какой-то стадии
where somewhere it will be a project already
где где то это будет проект уже
known ready-made working somewhere it
известные готовые работающие где то это
will be just ideas somewhere there will be from the
будет просто идеи где-то будут с камеры
camera because then there will be no one
вот потому что то уже не будет никто их
there will not be a week date considering
не будет недели дата считая
they are responsible  func filed here at
ответственость они func подав вот при
the same time they will appear they will
этом таки будут появляться они будут
appear and step on and appear on
появляться и наступи и появляться на
flexion all many will appear and we
флексия все многие будут появляться и мы
cannot be responsible for the fact that the
не можем нести ответственности за то что
project is that this project is good, too,
проект это что этот хорош проект тоже
as now I am not weak there we are the
как сейчас я не слаб там есть мы
number of hundreds of thousands of dockers here  and no
количество сотен тысяч докеров вот и как
matter how far from the fact that all these points
бы далеко не факт что вы все эти точки
are waiting for you to be a wild success,
на ждет бешеный успех
but I’ll probably add that
но я добавлю еще наверно что
in addition to just coping with this
помимо вот как раз бы справляться этой
mass of tokens, and again, the fact that our
массы токенах и опять же то что наша
user asks us, we will
пользователя нас просят мы будем
add a
добавлять
custom list of tokens that will be
кастомные списке токенов которые будут
managed by the
управляться
community  be managed very according to the
комьюнити будет управляться очень по
lady, etc., that is, you, as a
даме так далее то есть вы как
user, will be able to add a
пользователь сможете добавить к себе
list of tokens to yourself, thus taking
список токенов беря на себя таким
responsibility  for our
образом ответственность за собственные
own tokens that we ourselves with
те токины которые сами которыми с
which you work with, we sell you
которыми вы работать мы продаём вам
convenience in the interface
удобства в интерфейс
next
следующий вопрос
question  way, of
же способом не могут
course, the fat itself at the level of its
там конечно сама сало на уровне на своих
updates of its functions will very seriously
апдейтов своих функций очень серьезно
substitute the project and, of
подставим проект и
course, this could have been avoided
конечно этого можно было бы избежать
if the project was targeted were
если бы проект это таргетированные были
notified of such objects down
уведомлены таких объектах
there, look deeper now,
там низко поглубже посмотрите сейчас
there are bridges
есть бриджи
that have the right to be so
которые имеют право быть такими
due to this they  they can
за счет этого они могут фланга без
move the active flank without limits, but still don’t
лимитов перемещать активное но таки не
release on bail that they have these
выпускать под залог того что у них эти
lines, I’m not afraid, or let’s get a
строки не боюсь либо появится давайте
big reputation to do such things, but
большая репутации такие вещи делать а
that’s cool, that is, I don’t know, we
вот и круто то есть не знаю у нас ближе
often get stuck on the bolts, yes,
часто застревает счет на болтах да
because there is not enough elevator in  second
потому что мало лифте во вторых
is
находится
we could also in theory start
мы могли бы также в теории начать
releasing toke  we know that we have
выпускать токены знаю что у нас на
girlfriends flowing over others to plow the tokin
других во пахать токина лежат подруги
creates a potential
потоки над создает потенциальная
critical huge visibility that the
критическую огромную зримость которая
names in the field worked so we definitely
имена в поле сработала поэтому мы точно
don’t have it and I hope we won’t
не имеете вот и надеюсь надеюсь не будем
see the
видеть
edges ourselves so large that it
края сами настолько большими чтобы это
can be done
можно было делать
here it is there first  a fundamental
вот это вот там первым фундаментальным
fundamental reason why
фундаментальная причина почему такой же
we can’t attack with the same reciprocity here is the
взаимностью у нас атаковать нельзя вот
second second reason - this is the limit, yes,
вторая вторая причина-это то лимита да
that is, there were no limits at night,
то есть там ночью на лимитов не было
maybe there were limits on transfers,
может быть лимиты были на трансферах на
there were no limits on mente, and that’s
не было лимитах на mente а вот и поэтому
why such a hack would work
сработала который бы так такой хак
worked
сработал
I want .  that we, despite the fact that
я хочу . что мы несмотря на то что
such a specific vulnerability
подобная конкретно уязвимость в нашем
is impossible in our case, we constantly do
случае невозможно мы постоянно делаем
audits and security in jan, that is, we
аудит и безопасности при джан то есть
constantly pick externally teams are
постоянно ковыряем внешне команды
constantly trying to find vulnerabilities and,
постоянно пытаются найти уязвимости и
accordingly, only last year,
соответственно только за прошлый год
how many upgrades do you like 3 or 4 times
сколько на 3 или 4 раза апгрейда любишь
when we closed critical
когда нам мы закрывали критические
vulnerabilities like this, and for the past
уязвимости подобное вот и последние
few months, not a single such dimness
несколько месяцев ни одной такой димости
has been found, however, I remind you
найдено не был тем не менее я напомню
that we have a bounty program on
что у нас действует баунти программу на
enif for white hat hackers who
энифе для white hat хакеров которые
will be able to detect such a zira, give a
будут способны обнаружить такую зиру дай
vulnerability, so you can contact us via mini
уязвимость вот и с нами можно через мини
fly
fly связаться
if winter  here to me to be confirmed then
если зима здесь мне быть подтверждена то
there are quite good rewards
там достаточно хорошим вознаграждений
here and we are very serious i.e. the
вот и мы очень серьезно то есть у
security of funds and therefore sometimes
безопасности средств и поэтому иногда
our some security measures could
наши некоторые меры безопасности мог
turn out to be paranoid yes well it’s
оказаться параноидальными да ну лучше
better than losing money
так чем потерять деньги
so we are very responsible in this regard
поэтому мы в этом плане очень
i.e. the money of our
ответственно то есть деньгам наших
users
пользователей
thanks for  mind is the answer is special  but
спасибо за разум это ответ особенно
regarding the bar bounty program,
касательно программа бар баунти
I thought they said to do it completely
я думала говорят вообще полностью
on some separate one, in
сделать на какой-то отдельный на самом
fact, it was written about it about it
деле про это про это писалось про это
quite actively announced at the
достаточно активно анонсировалась в
beginning of last year with the program it will soon
начале прошлого года с программе скоро
be a year, in fact, during this time there
уже год будет самом деле за это время не
was not a single
было ни одного
reported bug  the anniversary program
заявленного бага программу
additionally comprehended to make sure the
дополнительно постиг сделать обязательно
following question is
следующий вопрос
why rd umbridge is only for those who
почему rd амбридж только для тех кто
gave liquidity in July and August
давал ликвидность в июле и августе
2021, and if I used the bridge at my own
2021 года а если я юзал bridge на свой
peril and risk in April 21, the
страх и риск в апреле 21 года самая
very first version and gave liquidity
персию первую версию и давал ликвидна
Stanislav
станислав
forty thousand dollars,
сорок тысяч долларов
maybe too  you can come up with some kind of
может тоже можно придумать какое-то
image of a breach
изображение breach
ten times more than hitler if
раз в десять больше чем и гитлером если
if it worked for me about from the folder it worked for
если мне про из папку это работало
me only one person wrote and
мне только один человек писал и
privately the reward day now if the
приватно день вознаграждения вот если
author of the question is not the same person after
автор вопроса не тот же человек после
she writes and I will show the transactions
она пишет и покажу транзакции
empty with Eunice paws there  I am very glad that
пустая с юнис лапам там очень рад что
there were few such users, and then they were
было мало таких юзеров вот тогда еще
just screaming about the cinema, secondly, that  m
только-только вопит о кино во вторых там
there were no equal risks that arose when you were
не было равных рисков которые возникли
no
когда уже
longer formed in this way in our country,
не таким формировались на наш стране ты
and
а
that’s why there was no pickup truck
вот и поэтому там по пикапу не было
count as well as everywhere else,
посчитано также как везде
so if someone
поэтому кто-то если этом сильно много
put a lot on this, let him write there is a
много ставил пусть напишет есть
phallic reward to
фаллическое вознаграждения
hear the question of migration that is
слышать вопрос по миграции которая
planned  On the 12th,
запланирована 12 число
could you tell us step by step what
могли бы вы пошагово рассказать что
to do to use
делать пользоваться
Yes, look again, first of all, there is no need
да смотрите еще раз во первых не надо
to panic now to pull funds
сейчас паниковать вытаскивать средства
out of the floors, because there is not much point in this
из полов потому что смысла в этом
as soon as we launch a
особого нету как только мы запустим
new version of the tax already with support for
новую версию такса уже с поддержкой
new Turks, and with automatic
новых турки надо и с автоматической
conversion of
конвертации
somatic both  so sometimes a new
соматическим оба рейдом так иногда новой
version, we will definitely
версии мы обязательно
firstly make announcements of all our
во первых сделаем анонсы всех наших
groups, we will scatter all the announcements by groups
группах раскидаем все анонсы по группам
Iberian, which will contain, among other things,
иверский где будет в том числе
all the most detailed
содержаться все максимально подробная
instructions on what needs to be done
инструкция что теперь нужно сделать
globally now, it looks quite simple,
глобально она выглядит достаточно просто
that is, firstly, if you need some
то есть во первых если вас какие то
streams  farming you will need
потоки на стоят фарминга вам нужно будет
these streams  there is no pharming to pull them out on the
эти потоки нет фарминга вытащить на
current version of the dex, disband them into
текущей версии декса их расформировать в
basic tokens, that is, the basic tokens in
базовые токины то есть базовые токина в
this case will be on your wallet and
этом случае окажутся у вас на кошельке и
you just need to go with the same wallet
вам нужно просто с этим же кошельком
on the new version of the bix to do the
зайти на новой версии бикса его сделать
action in reverse order, that is, the
действие обратном порядке то есть
east will not warm up to the new
востоке не прогреется до нового
standard  you will also put them captivated by the
стандарта вы их также положите увлекли
type you will receive a token and put them in
типу вы получите токин и поставить их в
the same form that will just
те же самые форме которые будут просто
be new support the new version
уже новыми поддерживать новую версию
here globally nothing will change for the user
здесь глобально для пользователя ничего
and moreover the old version of the
не изменится и более того старая версия
dex will be supported for at
декса будет поддерживаться еще как
least four more months to
минимум четыре месяца чтобы дать
enable users to pick up
возможность пользователям забрать
the reward for farming that they have
награду за farming которые у них
to spend will be unlocked during this
провести будет разлочить в течение этого
period and also then it will be possible
периода и также потом можно будет
to upgrade the tokens will receive a reward
перейти обновить токены получит награду
on the new version of the dex, that is, the
на новой версии декса вот то есть
procedure is as simple as possible, we
процедура максимально простая мы
try to make it as seamless as possible
стараемся сделать максимально бесшовный
for users, and of course there will be
для пользователей вот и конечно будут
instructions and there will be strong support
инструкцией и будет у сильная поддержка
in chat if  something will not work out there
в чатах если что-то будет не получаться
will be questions please
будут возникать вопросы пожалуйста
come please ask questions to
приходите пожалуйста задавайте вопросы
everyone will help
всем поможет
thanks
спасибо
chat
чат
question the
вопрос
next question will be
следующий вопрос будет
either dixa yes oops if we bridge
либо дикса да опа раз таки нам bridge
here I am at home to what not
вот я дома до чего нет
if it is actually expedient then of
если это фактически целесообразно то
course why not this is expedient
конечно почему нет этом целесообразно
it happens with what
это бывает при чем
bubbles will start to work constantly now a
начнет сейчас постоянно работать пузырей
annoying wig will appear one question about guevara what do you say in the future of
гевара а что вы скажете в будущем
dealers is there a risk that
дилеров существует ли риск что монеты
evil hands can get coins from there again and the
оттуда опять смогут попасть злые руки и
action is a way to deal with this
действие способ с этим бороться
if you carefully observe the dealer
если внимательно понаблюдать за дилером
yes for the last six months then there is a trigger
да за последние полгода то там триггер
yes already  it’s agreed in the affiliate program
да уже сошлось вот в партнерке таким
, remember that they go there and the lower tokens don’t
туда помни ходят и низшего токены не
even get lucky lips, that’s how it was from
получают даже повезти губ вот был так от
earlier for sale covered with lajons, that’s
раньше на продажу покрыт lajons вот
prevalent
prevalent и
and also, well, a little whale at competitions, well, it
еще и ну немножко кит по конкурсам ну
just went a little, that is, speak C
прям немного шло то есть говори на си
plus minus everyone understood yes what  - then you
плюс минус все поняли да что-то кино ешь
don’t need to eat the movie left-right somehow we see how
влево-вправо не надо как-то мы видим как
to do this at the start  the whole composition
сделать на старте вот это целый состав
will increase to this well, that is,
будет увеличиваться этому ну то есть
it is unlikely that the money will go just somewhere
вряд ли деньги пойдут просто куда-то
now the
сейчас
question of renaming type 33
стоящей вопрос о переименовании тип 33
will or will not
будет или не будет
send them a technical error the
присылать их техническая ошибка
designer apparently thought that it was logical to
дизайнер видимо подумал что логично
rename the talkin'
переименовать talkin'
standard there is sip and for some reason this error
стандарт есть sip и почему-то эта ошибка
leaked into  interface it was not so
просочилась в интерфейс это было не так
firstly now I remind you that the standard
во первых сейчас я напомню что стандарт
is to indulge in the type only now it is
это предаваться тип только теперь этом
not it is the soil path itself translucent novel I will
нет он грунт тропу сам translucent роман
continue as it were and therefore the abbreviation
продолжу как бы и поэтому аббревиатура
type it will be saved
тип она сохранится
thanks with only a question here it
спасибо с лишь вопрос вот там нужно
will be necessary to return back the vvc itself migration
будет вернуть назад ввц сам миграции
we separately like  rarely regarding the loaf
мы отдельно как редко касательно батоном
and separately we will write you instructions on
и отдельно вас вам напишем инструкцию
what needs to be done, because inside ourselves
что надо сделать потому что внутри себя
we are still exploring the possibility of
мы пока что исследуем возможность
doing this without unfolding if
сделать это без разворачивания если у
we succeed, then of course
нас это получится то мы конечно таким
we will do this if we still
образом поступим если все-таки
need to unfold this wear then
потребуется развернуть этого wear потом
wrap it back into your brother  where the
завернуть обратно в брат ты where the мы
we will write like this if you need all the
так и напишем если вам случае все
instructions
инструкции будут
[laughter  ]
[смех]
unloved to change the
нелюбимыми менять
next question, too, with an increase in migration,
следующий вопрос тоже с рост по миграции
they are for Kazan for immigration developers,
они для казани для разработчиков
what will be the price, but at the
иммиграции какая будет цена но по на
start, when to leave in order to
старте когда выходить чтобы максимально
minimize the effect of
снизить эффект
IL.
и.л.
but look, firstly,
но смотрите мы во-первых
how bro vinegar will at least stand
как бро уксус как минимум будем стоять
liquidity to the last on the old
ликвидность до последнего на старых
pools just so that the
пулах как раз для таки для того чтобы
rest of the users do not get the
остальные пользователей не получили тот
same thermo no,
самый термо нет
as for the price that
то что касается цены которые будут
1 user will get up and in the new fist,
вставать 1 пользователь и в новых кулак
but probably logical  and the same price,
но наверно логического и той же цене
even if it happens differently, then
даже если это произойдет по другому то
arbitrageurs immediately run who immediately
тут же бегут арбитражники который сразу
express all this, you need to understand this,
все это выразить нужно это понимать
therefore it is unprofitable to repaint the price,
поэтому перекрашивать цену невыгодно
so most likely everyone will simply switch
поэтому скорее всего просто все перейдут
to the same price at which it was
на той же самой цене по которой она была
at the time of closing the
на момент закрытия
next question is that the groan with  sap apo
следующий вопрос что стон с sap apo него
you can't hear anything
ничего не слышно
acceptance is
акцепт
slowly developing there are several
потихонечку развивается есть несколько
commands that vox and integrate but for
команд которые vox и интегрируют но по
some reason
каким-то причинам
it's not very fast to do this greeting the
делать не очень быстро вот приветствие
product itself turned out to be quite
продукт сам по себе получился достаточно
interesting
интересным
it's a lightweight library that
это легковесный библиотека который
allows you to add support for
позволяет вам добавить поддержку
payments
платежей
iv type 3 faders you still need  they will be
фейдерах iv тип 3 таки надо они будут
updated, too, duty 3, well, literally a
обновляться тоже duty 3 ну буквально
few  for years, that is, it’s good for non-
несколько лет то есть это хорошо для не
complex
сложных сценариев
scenarios, and now at the moment we have been
вот и сейчас на данный момент мы
focusing exclusively on the pilot of
фокусировались исключительно с пилотом
this product within the community, then
этого продукта внутри комьюнити дальше
we will change the approach, obviously in general, in
мы будем менять подход очевидно вообще в
principle, for all our products, most
принципе для всех наших продуктов скорее
likely we will allow some kind of
всего мы будем допускать какие-то
targeted hackathon contests for  for the
таргетированные хакатоны конкурсы на для
development of products using our
разработки продуктов использующих наше
solution, it’s possible that the rr acceptance
решение вот и возможно что р-р акцепт
will be
станет
at home, the board of the first ones appeared precisely
я дома доска первых именно появился
because in a row that you can
потому что ряду что можно его
drag it into different plugins drag
затаскивать в разные плагины затаскивать
it into wordpress designers too, that’s
в тоже на wordpress конструкторы вот
around the girl close solutions, so
вокруг девочка близко решений поэтому
here is our first then adat broke  so
здесь вот наш первых потом адат broke so
with our products,
с нашими продуктами
personally
лично
surveillance is just for the sent black
слежка просто для отправленных black
hole and the token there is a migration mechanic,
hole и токена есть механика миграции
well, I also already talked about this, most
ну я про это тоже уже говорил скорее
likely it will look like
всего оно будет выглядеть следующим
this, the creators of the original creators of the
образом создатели изначально создатели
currents,
токи
they will have to make a new version of the token
им придется сделать новую версию токина
through an updated builder, after
через обновленный builder вот после
that, the emission of talking which  should
этого то эмиссия talking который должна
be exchanged  on which right now in
быть обменен на которых вот сейчас в
free circulation in the hands of
свободном обращении на руках у
users should be placed on a
пользователей должно быть размещено на
special contract and in fact, the
специальном контракте и фактически то
benefit or that will bring
польза или которые принесут
tokenize the old version in this contract
tokenize старая версия в этот контракт
will automatically receive the token of the new version,
получит автоматом токина новой версии
so the creators can just transfer
вот создатели могут точно также передать
remember it
помнишь it
black hole now while this tool is in
black hole сейчас пока этот инструмент в
developing there, we’ll go down which one is better
разработке там еще сходим какие лучше
to do in any case, as soon as it was
сделать в любом случае как только он был
ready, and it will be exactly
готов а будет точно
before the end of the migration, it will appear here and
до конца миграции появится вот и
everything with all the instructions, we will explain
весь со всеми инструкций мы объясним как
how to use it to create
им пользоваться для создать
you tried to make it as simple as possible for
вы старались сделать это максимально
you, will l2 be
вас будет ли l2
with a Jew and if so  no, why was
с евреем и если да нет то почему
it given only by the
это давалось лишь на
smell of this site regarding the shard as the
запах этого сайта касательно шарды
hero of the shard it will be this we ourselves
героем шарда это будет вот это мы сами
will make rakus us now here guys
сделаем раксус нас сейчас вот ребята
jam to play type 3 then back to the completion of
джем играться тип 3 потом до завершения
most of the gimbal and after that
обратно most of кардана и после этого
again it is necessary to facilitate the work of
опять же то нужно для облегчения работы
immersion of new developers  in the birsk system the
погружение новых разработчиков в системы
next question will be whether the bridge and dex
следующий вопрос будет ли у моста и dex
yes cent  ralized access, and that is, the
да централизованным доступа а то есть
site will turn off then 99 percent of people
сайт и отключит то 99 процентов людей не
will not be able to have access to their funds,
смогут иметь доступ к своим средствам
so it is still there, please all
так он и сейчас есть пожалуйста все
interfaces are in the public domain is
интерфейсы в открытом доступе находится
on our github deploy your
на нашем гитхабе разворачиваете
own interface and use
самостоятельно интерфейс и пользуйтесь
the same dex yes for example this is
то же самое декса да например это
an alternative interface to those  by the very
альтернативный интерфейс к тем же самым
contract of you, customized with the talking list, the
контрактом вас кастомизированных списком
next question
следующий вопрос
will be able to make detailed instructions on how
сможете сделать подробную инструкцию как
to perform operations on dixie and a bridge through the
сделать операции над дикси и мосте через
tone by force, and in the case of a non-working
тонус силой а в случае не рабочего
web interface,
web-интерфейса
well,
ну
probably yes, the
наверное да
question of
вопрос
priority
приоритета
1 is just a task that fits well
1 это как раз задача которая хорошо
in the community, yes, that is, if  it’s
ложится в комьюнити да то есть если это
someone who will do everything to do it, we’ll show it, but by
кто-то сделает все делать покажем этим а
what,
чем
that is, I quit, you can’t do everything,
то есть бросил не можешь делать все
I’m sorry, I’ll explain now, maybe here we have
жалею я сейчас поясню может здесь у нас
a very large parity for this year
на этот год на самом деле очень большой
[music]
[музыка]
documentation and the principle of communication on
документации и принципе коммуникации по
our product, here we are fine
нашим продукт вот и мы прекрасно с вами
we see with you that in many blocks, but we did not
видим что по многим блоком но мы не
finalize last year, yes  because to
дорабатывали прошлом году да потому что
come those priorities were different,
прийти те приоритеты были другие вот в
this year we are focusing there and we
этом году мы там делаем фокус и нам
have to develop a huge
предстоит разработать огромное
amount of training materials on how to
количество обучающих материалов как по
use our products, such their
использованию наших продуктов такие их
use for developers, and
использования для разработчиков вот и
that’s why the description of one specific
поэтому и описание одного конкретного
case with tones of
кейса с тонов силой
power, well, the priority goes somewhere  in the end,
она ну приоритетом идет куда-то в конец
that is, simply because there are things that are
то есть просто потому что есть вещи
much
гораздо более
more pressing, the point is that by the
насущной особенность прицел на то что к
year we can have a fairly large
нам году может быть достаточно большое
number of new users, that's
количество новых пользователей вот
why, yes, we would be glad for any support
поэтому да мы будем рады любой поддержке
from the community, this would be our
с комьюнити бы это будет наш
next question, so after all, this is
следующий вопрос так все-таки это
about  bots over it is weak, does it still
касательно ботов над он слаб все-таки
have to fight for relation to
имеет ли бороться за отношение к
any bot over it is weak, well
каким-либо ботом над он слаб ну своих
, we don’t have our own bots, that is, only those
ботов у нас нет то есть только те
that we use for automation
которые мы используем для автоматизации
inside the Brooks system again, but there is
внутри системы бруксу снова но там
now a plugin that would connect the
сейчас плагин который бы соединялся
planet here are others less  known
планету вот других менее известных
when listing ja
когда листинге ja
let when listing bridge and let
позволь когда листинге бриджа и позволит
them the new format closely zd  here they carved a
им новый формат тесно здесь высекали
brother!  tells the guys
брата ! рассказывает ребята
everything went it’s impossible because there
все пошло это невозможно потому что там
is a part not just a smear
есть часть не то мазком
about the bridge hike less about that one is ready in the
про поход бриджа менее с про тот готов в
obse just not about the bridge but here it’s possible
обсе лишь не про bridge а тут возможно
but you just need to know the sequence of the
но просто нужно знать последовательность
call
вызов
here you maybe we don’t have Moscow
вот вам возможно нами то москве нет
at all and the science of the gap is metal  itself
вообще и наука бреши это металл сам
so the
так
question was answered when the listing of the bridge
вопрос ответили когда листинге бриджа
say it has a lot of hold and will allow but the
сказать имеет много держи и позволит но
format of the tag to shake the same on the supporter of the
формат тег трясти таки на сторонник
exchange
биржа
dex can be
dex может быть
given let's work on it and sing
дано дайте над этим мы работаем и спеть
such that's all that's the standard here with but the
такие вот все вот стандарт вот с но
standards let's try already on
стандартам да будем пробовать уже по
completion on the exchange and  there to do a
совершению на бирже и там делать делать
listing with a substance, including a program, a pledge, we are
листинге веществом числе программа зарок
operating now, this means you are sleeping with me,
оперируем сейчас это значит со мной
but because, but we all need
спишь а вот потому что но нам надо все
to go out for sex
выходить на сексу постепенно
gradually, these exits to the sex of these 3 exchanges, that
вот эти выходы на секс этих 3 бирж то
is, some kind of donation runs, it will
есть какие-то дарственной бежит
support some earlier, because
поддержит раньше какие-то то потому что
small but the number of tasks and we are
небольшими но число задач и мы
engaged in
занимаемся
hq will be into the void the token
hq будет будет into the void токин
will automatically sweep in contrast to the
автоматически пронесутся в отличие от
body provided by the liquid  there is no identity,
тела предоставляемой ликвидности
I said that in the world record
нет я же говорил что in the world record
it will gradually become a client if you
постепенно перейдет в он клиент если вы
can pick it up from old firms, that is,
сможете ее забрать старых фирм то есть
it will be separated in accordance with the
она будет разлучиться в соответствии с
settings of the whole ing, that is, on those
настройками весь инга то есть на тех
pools that are controlled by defoliants, it is
пулах которыми управляют дефолианты это
120 days, that is, responsibly from the moment
120 дней то есть ответственно с момента
when
когда
accrual of rewards on farms will
начисление награды на фермах будет
stop counting 120 days the
остановлено считать 120 дней будет
rewards will gradually unfold and
постепенно разворачивается награды и ее
we will need to close it ourselves and
нужно будет закроем самостоятельно и
go to upgrade on the new version of the
пойти проапгрейдить на новой версии
swap
свопа
from igor a bridge you need to get the king sheets a
от игоря a bridge надо листы king
good question probably yes
хороший вопрос наверное да
because this one will also be affected by the
потому что этот его тоже затронет
update
обновление
will there be any  there will be an update
будет ли какой-то будет обновление
basically, of course, look now, just
основном конечно смотрите сейчас просто
you understood what is happening and
вы понимали что происходит и ведется
a lot of work is being done to prepare the
очень большая работа по подготовке
migration, that is, we have been doing this work
миграции то есть мы эту работу делаем
for the last month, and some other
уже последний месяц вот и какие то еще
things are still being analyzed
вещи до сих пор анализируется
directly this week to
непосредственно на этой неделе чтобы
understand how some things will be
понимать как будут какие-то вещи
will be completed and in all elements
завершатся и по всем элементам
connected with the work of our  of course,
связан с работой наших продуктов конечно
we will provide full instructions for their products
мы предоставим полную инструкцию
, some products have actually
какие-то продукты на самом деле апдейт
received an update, for example, or the same role
уже получили например или роли ту же
keeps Tokyo of the new standard for
удерживает токио нового стандарта на по
now, these talking are not yet here, but they
сейчас еще этих talking нет вот но они
already automatically shine their
уже автоматом сияют свой
question for what other missing docks the code
вопрос за какие еще недостающие доки код
you are ready to reward  the community
вы готовы вознаградить комьюнити
their location they are
расположение их их на самом деле много
actually missing a lot of things and in fact if the
чего не хватает и на самом деле если
initiative group comes and says that the
инициативная группа придут скажет что
guys we are ready to take on the circulation of the
ребята мы готовы взять на себя тираж
cup quest for
чашки квест по вот этим вот этим
these things, for example, then we certainly won’t leave
например вещам то мы конечно не оставим
it, I won’t send a
это не пошлю
deployed bridge adex, you need to enter
развернутый bridge adex надо войти
Yes, the
да
new version will be deployed, you need to find
новая версия будет развернуто надо найти
it, maybe even already deployed,
может быть даже уже развернуто вот будем
will we support this big one or will it by
ли мы и поддерживать это большое или он
chance hardly be considered
случайно вряд ли будет считаться
stable
стабильным
as a principle in any crowd,
как принципе в любом теснить
so the main list of questions ended,
так закончился основной список вопросов
these were questions of the blue succubus,
это были вопросы суккуба
you want to add
синего хотите что-то добавить
something last
последок
thanks  we want to say such
спасибо хотим сказать такой
an exhaustive list of questions it
исчерпывающий список вопросов
is really interesting to see sp  ectr
самом деле интересно видеть спектр
mood as far as how people
настроение насколько как бы люди
closely follow what is happening with the
внимательно следят за тем что происходит
network, it’s
сетью
surprising that there weren’t so many
удивительно что как было не так много
questions about our kind, this one because
вопросов по нашему роду эту вот потому
I expected a little more activity in
я ожидал немножечко больше активности в
this direction, but in principle it turned out to be
этом направлении но в принципе получился
very
очень интересным
interesting this year as we saw a lot  what
в этом году как увидели у нас много что
is planned,
планируется
I hope that this will allow the network as a whole,
я надеюсь что это позволит сети в целом
I’m always that definitely stronger, yes, that is, because
я вечно тот точно сильнее да то есть так
due to the fact that he was there until December and the
из-за того чтобы он там по декабрь и
figure for the pores of January, they also
фигуре за порах января тоже поздно
came out late then to the tape 3 there were very
выходили потом тону ленте 3 был очень
few communications scam unity
мало коммуникаций скам unity
here you are trying  correct and therefore there
вот пытаешься исправить и поэтому много
were a lot of questions that came out on my
было пьешь вопросов которые вышли на мой
end, it’s a little off topic, in
итоге она немножко не по теме на самом
fact, that is, there were words in scope
деле то есть там в размахе были были
that we had very strange
слова которые мы которым очень странно
questions, there was no
вопросов не было
place and private grumblings and whiskey or yes
местом и частные бурчи и на виски или да
and I’m the yandex myth here  these are things that you
и я мифа yandex вот это вещи которые ты
did not ask, therefore, but well, therefore, but
не спросил поэтому но хорошо поэтому но
they will remain for later on next to
они уже на потом останутся на следующую
him
ему
about it, or make the lip appear there already
об этом либо сделать губа уже там
d  for more detail here and
появится для большей детализации там и
there, this story is huge,
там буду это эта история огромное
and I probably also wanted to say a few words
да и еще я наверно хотел два слова
about the format of
сказать по формату
promo sessions,
промо сессий
we will modify it a little bit,
мы его будем немножечко видоизменять вот
so we urge everyone to do the same, in fact, first of
это же призываем делать на самом деле
all, to hold them
всех остальных во первых проводить их
more often, that is, to hold them  not
чаще то есть это и проводить их не
only within the
только внутри комьюнити
Iberian community, respectively, we now
иверский la соответственно у нас сейчас
have a very large plan to go
есть очень большой план по выходу за
beyond the world of skill and conduct
пределы мир скилла и проведению амасии
other projects in the Amasia community, and plus,
комьюнити других проектов вот и плюс ко
they will be little studied, that is,
всему они будут малоизученными то есть
they will either be English-speaking or
они будут либо англоязычными либо
Truskavets, that is, we will most likely
трускавец то есть мы будем скорее всего
share to  do not discriminate against
разделять чтобы не дискриминировать те
certain community groups
или иные группы сообщества
[music]
[музыка]
thank you very much thank you 6 a day
спасибо большое вам спасибо 6 в день вот
I'm very grateful that you came and answered the community's question I also wanted to remind you that we will have an English-language ama session well, it seems to me that we should also
ну и мне кажется что надо тоже
switch to rooms of this
переходить к комнатам такому
format  where
формату где
the most active questions
самые самые такие активные вопросы
would also like you encouraged
тоже бы как ты поощрялись
users motive  it works like this, it
пользователей мотивирует вот как
worked correctly so in general the
правильно работала так в целом
photo of everyone up to 100 global turned around
фото всех до 100 глобальный повертелся
allowed a couple of minutes to say a few
позволили пару минут сказать несколько
things we have several birth injuries
вещей у нас есть несколько травм родовых
before which we are trying to fix something the
до которые что-то мы пытаемся исправить
children even started and what concerns the
дети даже и начинали да то что касалось
global static experiment
глобального со статического эксперимента
with partner dogs that  led
с собаками партнерками что привело к
to the fact that there was a lot of token on the river
тому что на реке оказалось много токина
just like that, yes, well, it’s
просто так да ну это
more or less the tap is turned off now, tokens
более-менее кран перекрыт сейчас токены
just don’t go to the market
на рынок просто так почти не выходят
after the end of the reforms, otherwise the piston,
после окончания реформ на иначе пистон
that is, they will only be for
как то есть таки на будут только за
really done, it’s important not for promises
реально сделанный важно не за обещания
for made  removable stories are 1 1 1
за сделанные съемные истории это 1 1 1
thesis and the second we have a huge birth
тезис а второе у нас огромная родовая
trauma in communications, that is, this
травма в коммуникациях то есть это
applies not only to external communications
касается не только внешних коммуникациях
from watermelon communications,
из арбузных коммуникаций
and we all suffer from this and
причем этим страдаем мы все и
threw abs and not fondation and about Windows
бросил abs и не fondation и про винда
resources at the expense of the corpus I don’t know
ресурсов за счет корпус не знает вот я
them  out of the corner of my eye I saw something very
их краем глаза видел что-то очень
cool and interesting and the poet of communication
прикольно интересно и поэт коммуникации
no
нет
photos in the box 57 projects here too  no
фоток в боксе 57 проектов вот тоже никто
one knows, we don’t even
не знает мы даже последствии от
know how to tell the consequences of the development, so
разработки не умеем рассказывать поэтому
here we will try to cure ourselves first
здесь мы попробуем сначала себя вылечить
, then it will be difficult for us to sag on
вот потом на нам сложно будет провисать
others to advise, and this is about
другим советовать вот и это про
changes in streams massive, that is, we are
изменения стримов массовая то есть мы
now trying to do inside ourselves
сейчас пытаемся сделать внутри себя
so that the information goes better what
чтобы информация ходила лучше то что
makes it  what tells after that that
делает это что велит после этого чтобы
it should go to the community and after that
это уходило в коммьюнити и после этого
that it should go to the outside world and
чтобы это уходило во внешний мир и
change formats, we will experiment
смена форматов будем экспериментировать
now, that is, the boards have already started a filter, I
сейчас то есть плат уже завел фильтр я
will still accurately start twitter with that
все-таки точным заведу twitter с тем
good
хороший
cheese you were taken away for quotes to
сыр тебя за цитаты растаскивали
deliver did did a lot of
поставлять делала делал много
similar  to overcome and communication
подобных преодолевать да и коммуникацию
to make the outside world because we are certainly
делать внешний мир потому что мы конечно
very weak in delivering our
очень слабый в том чтобы доставлять наш
result to the outside,
результат вовне
that's why we make this wave of changes with us through
вот поэтому эту волну изменений у нас
communications we make them good
коммуникациями мы их делаем хорошие
products a matter for a reliable solution
продукты делом для надежное решение
relates to doing well to tell and
относится поступает хорошо рассказать и
here too everyone can help you
здесь тоже все можете помогать вы же
see  often people come with some kind of
видите часто приходят люди с какими-то
initiative
инициативами
you, or they say that there is some kind of
вот или говорят что есть какая-то
problem, yes, you are calling on all problems
проблема да ты призывая всех проблем
to start solving, that is, problems with
начать решать то есть проблемы с
documentation problems with the appearance on
документацией проблемы с появлением на
all sorts of different foresters,
всяких разных лесниках
please contact it better to
обратитесь лучше это сделать не просто
do this  it was also
писали это это не работает это тоже было
checked older, here it is coordination
проверено старше вот она координация
can be through people from the alliance and
может быть через людей из альянсом и
I think we will also publish decay
думаю тоже опубликуем матрицы распад
matrices assemble the agency who is responsible for what
соберите агенция кто за что отвечает то
what it
что делает
does that was who to contact according to a clear
вот что было кому обращаться по понятным
task scheme here are the mechanics of encouraging both
схему задач вот механики поощрения как
individual brooks and from the alliance
индивидуальных брукс так и от альянса
if it concerns  we will also
если это касается все сети тоже будем
try to describe all the networks so that everyone
стараться их описать с тем чтобы все
understands, but for now, it’s still basic,
понимали но пока базово пока это еще
if it’s not fully described, you can
если это не описано полностью до можете
start contacting some
начать обращаться к каким-то бот
Valencia bots and they will be in a new one, you
валенсия и будут будут в новую еще то
can decide to start doing this, you
можете решить сделать начать это делать
can write to me in time  day and night yes
можете писать мне времени дня и ночи да
I address where you need to go home then
я адресую туда куда надо домой тогда
you can through the novel the second level is
можно можно через роман втором уровне
always in touch
всегда на связи
yes
да
about  I draw you there
обрисую вас туда